https://www.tervis.com/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
Tervis wants to make your online experience pleasant, convenient and safe. "Personal information" is information about an identifiable individual, which includes name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, and other information that is identifiable to you, as more particularly defined by privacy legislation. By using our Website, or by providing us with your personal information at our stores, in our promotions and in other ways when you interact with us, you signify your agreement and acceptance to the conditions stated in our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information provided to us in connection with employment opportunities.
What Kind of Information Does Tervis Collect?
Tervis collects the personal information you provide us in connection with your purchase transaction, such as your name and telephone number. We also collect and maintain records and history about customers' purchases and product preferences. If you pay by credit card, debit card or check, you provide us with your account information. If you return merchandise or request a refund or exchange, you provide us with your personal information. Also, when you register or create an online account with us, sign up for e-mail, contact Customer Service, participate in our surveys, enter our sweepstakes, contests or other promotions, or send us feedback or submissions, you are providing us with your personal information. Tervis does not collect or transit any camera or video/audio data, we only provide the ability to take a screenshot within the mobile Tervis app.
How Does Tervis Use My Information?
When we collect information from you, such information may be used for one or more of the following reasons:
process and complete your purchase transaction
identify your product and service preferences so that we can notify you of new or additional products, services and promotions that might be of interest to you
improve product offerings and customer service
notify you about new services, features, promotions and special offers that Tervis thinks you will find valuable
respond to your inquiries
measure the advertising effectiveness of our online and other advertisements and offers
customize the advertising and services you see
conduct research
help us understand Website activity and improve your use of our Website
collect aggregated site-visitation statistics
help us prevent fraud and minimize credit risk
In order for us to maintain the accuracy of your personal information and improve our communication with you, we may also combine the information we collect with other public demographic information. On rare occasions we may also be required to disclose your information as is required by law pursuant to lawful requests such as subpoenas, court or agency orders, or as we may reasonably determine to be necessary to protect our rights or the rights of others, to avert harm to persons or property, or to enforce the Website Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy.
How Does Tervis Use "Cookies"?
We and some of our third-party service providers use "cookies". A "cookie" is a small text file written by an Internet server to a Website user's browser where information is exchanged between them, and which is stored on a computer's hard drive to allow us to recognize and track users on our Website to assist us in providing our customers with a productive online experience. Cookies enable us to store information about your use of our Website, such as the areas you visit and the length of your stay. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies and can be reset by using the 'Help' portion of the toolbar to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. Should you choose to disable any cookies associated with the Website, you will not be able to take full advantage of all the Website's features, but you should be able to navigate the Website without difficulty.
Does Tervis Share My Information With Third Parties?
We may share certain personal information we collect about you with third parties who perform services for us or with whom we contract for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. For example; we may use third parties to host our Website, operate certain features, send e-mails, print our mailings, run our sweepstakes, contests or other promotions, authorize and process your payments, and analyze data and our advertising effectiveness. These third-party service providers are given the information they need to perform their designated functions and we do not authorize them to use or disclose your personal information for their own or any others' marketing purposes.
Your information may also be transferred as an asset in connection with a merger or sale (including any transfers made as a part of an insolvency or bankruptcy proceeding) involving all or part of Tervis or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale or other change in corporate control.
Is My Information Safe With Tervis?
Protecting your personal information is important to us. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect your online order information as it is transmitted over the Internet. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. To support this technology, users must have an SSL-capable browser. While we use such sophisticated security technology to secure users' ordering information, user name, and password, we cannot guarantee that any electronic commerce is totally secure.
To check the security of your connection, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser window after accessing the server. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser), then SSL is active. You can also double-check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from 'http' to 'https.'
If your browser or firewall doesn't support SSL, you will not be able to connect to the server, which means you won't be able to mistakenly place an order through an unsecured connection. If you cannot access the secure server for any reason, please place your order by phone at 1-866-886-2537.
You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your user name, password, and any account information. It is important for you to be responsible and protect your user name, password, and computer against unauthorized users. It is important to sign off when you have completed using a computer accessible by others. Please see the Website Terms of Use for further details.
How Do I Opt-Out From Tervis Email?
You may opt-out of receiving promotional email from us by doing one of the following:
If you originally signed up for Tervis email, please return to the email sign-up page, and complete the 'unsubscribe' entry field and click the "Unsubscribe" button. Please be sure to use the same email address as that which you used to sign-up. Otherwise it may not be possible to comply with your request.
If you have received an email from Tervis, you can follow the opt-out or 'unsubscribe' instructions provided in your e-mail.
How does Tervis Protect Kids' Privacy?
We are concerned about the safety of children when they use the Internet and will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. Users of the Website must be at least eighteen years old. If a child has provided us with personal information, that child's parent or guardian should contact us at CustomerCare@tervis.com to delete such information from our records.
Changes to Our Policy
If you have any questions about our privacy policy, you can always contact Tervis.com Customer Care in any of these three (3) ways:
Send us an email message at CustomerCare@tervis.com
Call us at 1-866-886-2537
Write to us at:
Tervis Tumbler Company
201 Triple Diamond Blvd.
North Venice, FL 34275
